Some customer emails are a breeze.
Short, clear, easy to process. But
others, not so much. Long descriptions,
mismatching names, vague references.
Suddenly, you're spending time
deciphering, searching, even chasing the
customer for clarification.
That's exactly the kind of challenge the
sales order agent was built to handle.
Inside Business Central, the sales order
agent carefully processes the email and
presents a suggested result directly in
the agent pane. The agent had no issues
identifying both direct matches and
other items with matching
characteristics, checked their
availability, and prepared a ready to
send reply, saving lots of time, usually
spent reading and rereading the email,
looking up the items one by one. Curious
how it could be so thorough? It wasn't
just a simple search by description. The
agent uses multiple search parameters
across many sources to deliver the best
results such as the description,
additional description, GTN number, and
the item category code and description.
But it doesn't stop there. Also,
searching through supplemental data
linked to the items. In its search, it
considers item attributes like material,
size, color, weight, or dimensions,
which are especially helpful when
customers get specific in their
requests.
It also searches among item variants,
different versions of the same item in
Business Central, for example,
stationary or mobile models, or
variations in size, color, or style. The
search includes item identifiers,
alternative codes used for items in
Business Central, such as vendor
numbers, barcodes, or customer specific
codes that uniquely identify the item.
It also goes through item references.
Additional links in Business Central
such as customer item numbers or vendor
item numbers that help match the way
different parties refer to the same item
in their own systems.
Search includes the information captured
in the extended text and translations,
ensuring that these detailed
descriptions or requests in different
languages are analyzed to find the right
item match.
With its advanced search capabilities
powered by natural language
understanding, the agent can easily
recognize and find the requested items
where customers use their own codes or
other ways of naming items. It can
interpret those details, match them
against your data, and ensure nothing
gets lost in translation.
Clear or complicated, customer requests
get processed more efficiently, saving
your time and reducing back and forth,
adding more joy to your interactions
with your customers and with your
business central.